Deny nothing.
Burning Blue is a drama, romance, war film directed by D.M.W. Greer.
Two Navy fighter pilots find themselves in the midst of a forbidden
relationship throwing their lives and careers into disarray.
Daniel Lynch, played by Trent Ford.
Susan Sephensen, played by Tammy Blanchard.
William Stephensen, played by Morgan Spector.
Matthew Blackwood, played by Rob Mayes.
Charlie Trumbo, played by William Lee Scott.
Admiral Lynch, played by Cotter Smith.
Burning Blue is a 2013 American United States Naval
aviation drama film, directed by D.M.W.
Greer and starring Trent Ford and Rob Mayes.
The film is based on the 1992 play of the same name by Greer about a U.S.
Navy accident investigation which becomes a gay witch hunt
during the "Don't Ask, Don't Tell" era.
The film explores themes of secret love, pilot,
forbidden love, melancholy, u.s. navy.
The tone is emotional and intense.